export const quiz = {
  totalQuestions: 20,
  questions: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "What is the generic name for the drug Lipitor?",
      answers: ["Atorvastatin", "Simvastatin", "Rosuvastatin", "Lovastatin"],
      correctAnswer: "Atorvastatin",
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "Which drug classification is used to treat hypertension?",
      answers: ["Statins", "Antifungals", "Antivirals", "ACE inhibitors"],
      correctAnswer: "ACE inhibitors",
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'What does the abbreviation "qhs" stand for?',
      answers: ["Every hour", "Every day", "At bedtime", "As needed"],
      correctAnswer: "At bedtime",
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question:
        "Which of the following medications is a proton pump inhibitor?",
      answers: ["Omeprazole", "Metformin", "Loratadine", "Acetaminophen"],
      correctAnswer: "Omeprazole",
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "What is the primary purpose of a pharmacy technician?",
      answers: [
        "To prescribe medications",
        "To diagnose illnesses",
        "To assist the pharmacist in dispensing medication",
        "To perform surgeries",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "To assist the pharmacist in dispensing medication",
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "Which category of drugs is used to relieve pain?",
      answers: ["Analgesics", "Diuretics", "Antidepressants", "Antihistamines"],
      correctAnswer: "Analgesics",
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "What is the brand name for the drug alprazolam?",
      answers: ["Xanax", "Valium", "Prozac", "Zoloft"],
      correctAnswer: "Xanax",
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question:
        "Which of the following is a common side effect of corticosteroids?",
      answers: [
        "Increased appetite",
        "Decreased heart rate",
        "Insomnia",
        "All of the above",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "All of the above",
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: 'What does the term "contraindication" mean?',
      answers: [
        "A reason to take a medication",
        "A reason to avoid a medication",
        "A side effect of a medication",
        "None of the above",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "A reason to avoid a medication",
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: 'What is the common use for the drug class "beta blockers"?',
      answers: [
        "Lowering blood pressure",
        "Treating depression",
        "Relieving pain",
        "Treating infections",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Lowering blood pressure",
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "Which medication is used to treat Type 2 diabetes?",
      answers: ["Metformin", "Warfarin", "Lisinopril", "Amoxicillin"],
      correctAnswer: "Metformin",
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "Which of the following is an opioid medication?",
      answers: ["Morphine", "Losartan", "Levothyroxine", "Lisinopril"],
      correctAnswer: "Morphine",
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      question: 'What does "PO" stand for in medical terminology?',
      answers: ["By mouth", "By injection", "By rectum", "By inhalation"],
      correctAnswer: "By mouth",
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      question: "What is the role of an antibiotic?",
      answers: [
        "Relieve pain",
        "Reduce inflammation",
        "Fight bacterial infections",
        "Lower cholesterol",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Fight bacterial infections",
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      question: "Which medication is used to treat allergic reactions?",
      answers: ["Epinephrine", "Lorazepam", "Metoprolol", "Simvastatin"],
      correctAnswer: "Epinephrine",
    },
    {
      id: 16,
      question: "Which of the following medications is an anticoagulant?",
      answers: ["Warfarin", "Metformin", "Atorvastatin", "Furosemide"],
      correctAnswer: "Warfarin",
    },
    {
      id: 17,
      question: 'What does "PRN" stand for in medical terminology?',
      answers: ["Every day", "As needed", "Before meals", "After meals"],
      correctAnswer: "As needed",
    },
    {
      id: 18,
      question: "Which medication is used to treat high cholesterol?",
      answers: ["Atorvastatin", "Metformin", "Lisinopril", "Amoxicillin"],
      correctAnswer: "Atorvastatin",
    },
    {
      id: 19,
      question: 'What does the term "bioavailability" mean?',
      answers: [
        "The amount of drug that is excreted",
        "The amount of drug that is absorbed and available for use",
        "The amount of drug that is metabolized",
        "The amount of drug that is prescribed",
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        "The amount of drug that is absorbed and available for use",
    },
    {
      id: 20,
      question: "Which medication is typically used to treat epilepsy?",
      answers: ["Phenytoin", "Losartan", "Metformin", "Atorvastatin"],
      correctAnswer: "Phenytoin",
    },
  ],
};
